Now, it says, Create one Quarterly Target for each of your Core
4 Domains. So, if I click on this, I've already done this,
but you may go and see something different because you don't have
this.
So, if I look out to the future. It would look like
this, where we're, there's no plan for Q4, and you're going to
go step-by-step, and it's going to walk you through with the power
of AI to help you brain dump ideas for each area, set
monthly missions, set quarterly targets, give you clarification to
make sure that they are measurable, and trackable, and then also give
you daily ideas for habits that you can do to feed the
overall goal that you have, which is, could be weight loss, or
strength gain, or, you know, anything inside a body.
It could be a number of times that you're going to go
to church, or start a men's group, or start a church Bible
study group.
Or, if we go to balance, maybe it's a certain number of
date nights with your spouse over, over a quarter period, or maybe
you're trying to plan a big trip, and there's certain things that
you gotta do to get the trip and make it possible, you
can create those targets inside of that area.
Now, I have a, a dummy plan in here for, the quarter,
and once it's completed, it basically says, hey, your quarter is live,
do you want to look at it?
So, if I click on view my plan, I can see some
things that we plugged in here from a quarter perspective and how
this works.
So, I put in here, finish the Spartan race. That's my quarterly
target for this, this one. What's my July target?
Complete eight training sessions. Tracking workouts focused on obstacle course techniques. Logging
progress after each session. Ok. August, participate in two practice races.
September, complete the Spartan race, tracking, finishing time, and obstacles completed. So,
I have my targets for the monthly and then I could also
add daily proof in here if I wanted to say, you know,
these are the type of things I'm going to allocate into core
four every day to make sure it's feeding
the overall goal. So, here's another thing. If I'm trying to say,
I'm just trying to go to church four times.
It's going to get me in a position to make sure that
I'm doing those things that I said I want to do individually
to make sure it's actually here for me.
To actually read, right? So, now I continue down here. Balance. Have
10 to 12 date nights with my partner this quarter.
Aim for weekly. Now, it's breaking it down monthly. And again, finally,
business for new one-on-one clients. It's breaking down monthly, and I know
what my strategic monthly targets are.
Again, very, very transparent. It makes it very easy for you to
know what's going on. Now, monthly missions. That's the next thing.